Sierra Club, Atlantic Chapter; Records apap130
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- James Bay Hydroelectric Project, 1989-1994; 5; 3.77 cubic ft.
  - Cree Indians, Conferences and Meeting, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 38)
  - Cree Indians, Health and Sanitation, 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 39)
  - Cree Indians, The Nation (Cree Publication), 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 40)
  - Cree Indians, New York State Tour with Inuit, 1990; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 41-42)
  - Cree Indians, Press Coverage, 1990 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 43)
  - Cree Indians, Press Releases and Announcements, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 44)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1991 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 45)
  - Debate on Project at Cornell University, 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 46)
  - Declaration of Energy Independence, 1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 47)
  - Demand - Side Management, 1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 48)
  - Dinkins, David, 1991 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 49)
  - Earthbeat, Inc., 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 50)
  - Economic Impact, Undated (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 51)
  - Economic Studies of James Bay Project, 1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 52)
  - "Effects of Hydro-electric Projects on Hudson Bay's Marine and Ice Environments" by S.J. Prinsenberg (James Bay Publication Series #2), 1991 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 53)
  - Electricity Purchases from Outside the United States, 1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 54)
  - Energy Efficiency, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 55)
  - Energy Sources, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 56)
  - Environmental Impact Statements, 1991-1995; 9 folders (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 57-65)
  - Fact Sheets, ca. 1980s (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 66)
  - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 67)
  - Film about James Bay, 1997 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 68)
  - Goodman Group, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 69-70)
  - Great Whale Project Cancellation, 1994 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 71)
  - Great Whale River Tour, Undated (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 72)
  - Greenhouse Gases From Reservoirs Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 73)
  - Hoyt, William, 1992 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 74)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Advertisement, 1995 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 75)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Ballot Invitations for New York State Public Service Commission, 1993 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 76)
  - Hydro-Quebec, CEO/Chairman, 1991 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 77)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Electricity Export License, 1990 (Box 1 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 78)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Electricity Export License, 1994 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 1)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Electricity Export License, 1995 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 2)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Electricity Export Profitability, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 3)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Films and TV News Coverage, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 4)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Financial Activities Investigation, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 5)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Hydro-Quebec and the Environment, 1990 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 6)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Letter to Sierra Club, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 7)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Press Releases, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 8)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Proposed Hydro-Quebec Development Plan 1990-1992, Horizon 1999 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 9)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Security Force, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 10)
  - Hydro-Quebec, Testimony Before the New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 11)
  - Independent Power Producers of New York, 1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 12)
  - Lobbying, 1992; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 13-14)
  - Lobbying, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 15)
  - Long Island Lighting Company (LILCO), 1991; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 16-17)
  - Information Requests, 1994 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 18)
  - Inuit, Press Releases and Announcements, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 19)
  - "James Bay: A Call to Action", 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 20)
  - Legislation, Impact of Purchase of Electricity from Outside the United States on the Environment (A.2162-B (Hoyt et al)), 1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 21)
  - Long Run Avoided Costs (LRACS), 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 22)
  - Magnesium Imports from Canada, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 23)
  - Maps, James Bay Region, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 24)
  - Memoranda and Position Papers, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 27)
  - Native American Sites Committee, Sierra Club, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 28)
  - New York Power Authority, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 29)
  - New York Power Authority, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 30)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 31)
  - New York State Energy Planning, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 32)
  - New York State Energy Planning, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 33)
  - New York State Energy Planning, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 34)
  - New York State Legislature, Assembly, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 35-36)
  - New York State Legislature, Joint Legislative Hearing on Hydro-Quebec Contracts, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 37)
  - New York State Legislature, Senate, 1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 38)
  - New York Public Service Commission, 1991; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 39-40)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 41)
  - "Northern Rights Southern Light: Connections to James Bay", Undated (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 42)
  - Opimiscow/La Grande Agreement, 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 43)
  - Opposition Efforts, 1991 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 44)
  - O'Reilly/Mainville Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 45)
  - Origin of James Bay Project, 1976-1985; 1993 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 46)
  - Pace University School of Law, Center for Environmental Legal Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 47)
  - Petroleum Overcharge Restitutionary Plan, 1992 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 48)
  - Press Coverage, 1990 (Box 2 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 49)
  - Press Coverage, 1991; 4 folders (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 1-4)
  - Press Coverage, 1993 (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 5)
  - Press Coverage, 1994 (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 6)
  - Press Coverage, Criticism of, Undated (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1991-1993 (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 9)
  - Pros and Cons of Project, Undated (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 10)
  - Public Education, Organizing and Action Campaign, 1993 (Box 3 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 11)
  - Quebec, 1991 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 1)
  - Redford, Robert, 1991 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 2)
  - Revival of Project, 1997 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 3)
  - Rhode Island, 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 4)
  - Sainte Marguerite 3 Project, 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 5)
  - Sessions, Keiner, Dumont, Barnes and Everitt, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 6)
  - Sierra Club et al v. PASNY, 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 7)
  - Sithe Energies, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 8)
  - Strategy Meetings, 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 9)
  - Talking Points, 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 10)
  - "The Taming of James Bay" by Sean McCutcheon (Sierra), 1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 11)
  - Testimony by Sierra Club, 1992 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 12)
  - "The Trade Off between Economic and Environmental Objectives in Japan's Power Sector" by H. Amagai and P.S. Leung, The Energy Journal, 1991 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 13)
  - Update, 1995 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 14)
  - Vermont, 1990 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 15)
  - Walk in Prayer, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 16)
  - Wildlife, Impact upon, 1985; Undated (Box 4 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 17)
  - Hydro-Quebec Electricity Export License, Cree Appeal of, 1995 (Box 5 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 1)
  - Grande Baleine Complex Feasibility Study, 1993 August; 27 Volumes (Box 6 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 1)
  - Sainte Marguerite-3 Hydroelectric Development Project, 1993 August (Box 6 (5-James Bay Hydroelectric Pr), Folder 2)
    English and French copies.
- Publications, Sierra Club, 1970-1997; 6; 0.47 cubic ft.
  This series includes periodicals and single reports issued by both the Atlantic Chapter and the national Sierra Club. Periodicals put out by the Atlantic Chapter include The Argonaut (1970-1972 included here), Atlantic Chapter News Report (1986-1988, 1990), and Sierra Atlantic (1977-1982, 1984-1992, 1996). The Sierra Atlantic newsletters from Spring 2003 to the present are available online at http://newyork.sierraclub.org/Sierra%20Atlantic/index.htm.
  - Alaska Report, 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 1)
  - The Argonaut, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Chapter News Report, 1986-1988; 1990 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 3)
  - Danger in the Air, Hope on the Horizon, Great Lakes Program, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 4)
  - Darkening Skies: The Mounting Air Pollution Crisis in the United States, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 5)
  - Membergram, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 6)
  - National Wild and Scenic Rivers System, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 7)
  - Paradise Leased: Oil and Our Public Lands, 1987 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 8)
  - Planet: The Sierra Club Activist Resource, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 9)
  - Sierra Atlantic, vols. 4-7, 1977-1981 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 10)
  - Sierra Atlantic, vols. 8-9, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 11)
  - Sierra Atlantic, vols. 11-15, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 12)
  - Sierra Atlantic, vols. 16-19, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 1)
  - Sierra Atlantic, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 2)
  - Sierra Atlantic, Correspondence Regarding, 1987-1990 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 3)
  - The Sierra Club: A Guide, 1989 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 4)
  - Sierra Club California Legislative Agenda, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 5)
  - Sierra Club National News Report, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 6)
  - Sierra Club Waste Reduction News, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 7)
  - Winning with the Environment, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Publications, Sierra Club), Folder 8)
- Publications, Non-Sierra Club, 1979-1997; 7; 2.9 cubic ft.
  - Periodicals, 1979-1997; 7.1; 1.3 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains magazines focusing on topics of interest to the Atlantic Chapter (for example, Up River, Down River, a magazine about the Hudson River), or newsletters put out by other environmental organizations (e.g., Protectors of Pine Oak Woods, Toxics in Your Community Newsletter).
    - Adirondack Advocate (National Audubon Society), 1992-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 1)
    - Adirondack Council Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 2)
    - Adirondack Voices, 1992, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 3)
    - Albany County Soil and Water Conservation District News, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 4)
    - Alternatives/Policy Alternatives on Environment - A State Report (Center for Policy Alternatives), 1991-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 5)
    - The American Association for Fuel Cells Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 6)
    - American Water Resources Association, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 7)
    - Amicus/The Amicus Journal, 1979-1980; 1982; 1985 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 8)
    - Audubon Activist (National Audubon Society), 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 9)
    - Audubon Leader (National Audubon Society), 1991-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 10)
    - Auto-Free Press, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 11)
    - Beyond Beef, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 12)
    - CANnections (Clean Air Network), 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 13)
    - Capital Eye, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 14)
    - Catskill Center News, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 15)
    - Chlorine Free (Greenpeace), 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 16)
    - Citizens Campaign Report, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 17)
    - Citizens Campaign Report (Citizens Campaign for the Environment), 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 18)
    - Coalition Energy News (Coalition for Energy Efficiency and Renewable Technologies), 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 19)
    - Constitutional Matters, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 20)
    - Contact News 'N' Views Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 21)
    - Corollary (Houston Advanced Research Center), 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 22)
    - Council Contact (New York Metropolitan Transportation Council), 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 23)
    - Critical Mass (Public Citizen), 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 24)
    - Don't Waste New York Newsletter, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 25)
    - Down to Earth, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 26)
    - Earth Day News, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 27)
    - Eco-Politics, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 28)
    - The Empire Envoy Albany Update, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 29)
    - Empire State Report, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 30)
    - Environmental Business Association of New York State, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 31)
    - Environmental Law Section Journal, 1986; 1990-1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 32)
    - EPA Region 2 Highlights, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 33)
    - The ESPA Express, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 34)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 35)
    - Forest Reform Network, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 36)
    - Forest Voice, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 37)
    - From the Ground Up, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 38)
    - Global Environmental Change Report, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 39)
    - Government Law Center Newsletter, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 40)
    - Great Lakes United, 1988-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 41)
    - The Green Drummer, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 42)
    - The Green Sheet: Plugging Into New York's Environment, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 43)
    - High Ground: The Newsletter of the Highlands Coalition, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 44)
    - Hotline, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 45)
    - Inside EPA Weekly Report, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 46)
    - Lake Champlain/Lake George Regional Planning Board, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 47)
    - Land Use Law Reporter, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 48)
    - Learning Alliance, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 49)
    - Littorally Speaking, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 50)
    - Mobilizing the Region: A Weekly Bulletin from the Tri-State Transportation Campaign, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 51)
    - National Trails Day Update, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 52)
    - Natural Organic Farmers Association of New York State News, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 53)
    - New from Hudsonia, 1993; 1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 54)
    - New York State Audubon Advocate (National Audubon Society), 1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 55)
    - New York State Environment, 1995; 1997 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 56)
    - New York State Forum on Conflict and Consensus Newsletter, 1995? (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 57)
    - New York State Governmental Operations Committee Newsletter, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 58)
    - New York State Solid Waste Examiner, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 59)
    - New York Waste Reporter, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 60)
    - The Northeast Energy and Environment Report, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 61)
    - Northeast Farmland Update, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 62)
    - Pipeline, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 63)
    - Pollution Prevention (NYSDEC), 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 64)
    - Protectors of Pine Oak Woods, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 65)
    - RCRA Review, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 66)
    - Recycling Times, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 67)
    - Refuge Reporter, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 68)
    - Remediation Review, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 69)
    - Residents' Committee to Protect the Adirondacks Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 70)
    - River News: St. Lawrence - FDR Power Project Relicensing Update, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 71)
    - River Voices, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 72)
    - Scenic Hudson News, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 1)
    - The Siting Commission Newsline, 1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 2)
    - Sun Day Update, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 3)
    - Toxics in Your Community Newsletter, 1990-1995 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 4)
    - Toxics Progress Report, 1996 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 5)
    - Transportation Exchange Update, 1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 6)
    - Tug Hill Commission Newsletter, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 7)
    - United American Energy Corp. Profiles in Progress, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 8)
    - Up River/Down River, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 9)
    - Waste and Toxics Progress Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 10)
    - Water Bulletin (NYSDEC), 1991-1995 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 11)
    - Watershed, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 12)
    - Watershed Update, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 13)
    - Wild Earth, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 14)
    - Wild in New York (NYSDEC), 1992-1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 15)
    - The Woodlands Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 16)
  - Reports, 1980-1996; 7.2; 1.6 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains studies by various private organizations, as well as the New York State legislature and other state bodies, and the United States Environmental Protection Agency.
    - American Council for an Energy-Efficient Economy",Energy Efficiency as an Investment in Ohio's Economic Future", 1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 17)
    - American Lung Association Why Nox? The Costs, Consequences and Control of Nitrous Oxides in the Human and Natural Environment, 1989 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 18)
    - American Lung Association Your Health and Air Pollution, 1980 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 19)
    - American Lung Association of New York State/New York Environmental Institute Air Toxics in New York State: A Citizen's Guide to the Right-to-Know Law and Air Toxic Data, 1989 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 20)
    - Center for Policy Alternatives Policy Alternatives on the Environment: A State Report, 1992 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 21)
    - Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation Demand Side Management Evaluation, 1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 22)
    - Consumer Policy Institute/Consumers Union Toxic Chemical Accident Risks in New York City, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 23)
    - An Environmental Agenda for the Future by Leaders of America's Foremost Environmental Organizations, 1985 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Policy Institute Corporate Tax Policy and the Right to Know: Improving State Tax Policymaking by Enhancing Legislative and Public Access, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 25)
    - Greenpeace Fiscal Fission: The Economic Failure of Nuclear Power. Executive Summary, 1992 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 26)
    - National Audubon Society Listen to the Sound: A Citizens' Agenda: A Vision for Long Island Sound, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 27)